#### Contact

calliann54912247@aol.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sarahvarney-9a963ba8 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Healthcare

Nursing

Operating Room

Languages

English

Certifications
CNOR

# Sarah Varney

BSN, RN, CNOR, CSSM - OR Manager

Houston, Texas Area

### Summary

Experienced Registered Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in CNOR, Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), U.S. Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA), HMS, and Neurosurgery. Strong support professional graduated from New Mexico State University.

## Experience

Houston Methodist RN - Perioperative Services Manager May 2015 - Present (5 years 1 month) Houston, Texas

Currently manager over 30+ FTE's in a busy 24 hour operating room that focuses primarily on General and Neuro Surgery. In charge of payroll, promotion management and education management of staff. After hours management support for AOD, Pre-Op and PACU.

MountainView Regional Medical Center 4 years 10 months

RN - Breast Health Nurse Navigator July 2014 - April 2015 (10 months) Las Cruces, New Mexico Area

Assisting patients to navigate through the healthcare system. Building of a Breast Center Care program. I am also involved with the organization and running of our Tumor Board.

RN - Operating Room
July 2010 - July 2014 (4 years 1 month)

I functioned as OR circulator and scrub nurse for general and orthepedics cases incluiding total joints. I was also the evening Clinical Nurse leader for a time and a nurse educator, responsible for training our new graduate nurses.

Management duties included yearly evaluations of employees, time card approvals (Kronos), and staff scheduling.

Specialties included: pediatric dental procedures, ENT, GYN, GU, Thoracic, Vascular, Orthopedic, General. Have scrubbed and circulated orthopedics, general surgery cases, and DaVinci procedures.

Memorial Medical Center Las Cruces RN-Operating Room February 2007 - August 2010 (3 years 7 months)

I was a circulator, and preceptor for new graduates. I also was a cover charge nurse for both evening and day shift.

Specialties included: pediatric dental procedures, ENT, GYN, GU, Thoracic, Vascular, Orthopedic, General.

#### Education

Aspen University

Master of Business Administration - MBA, MBA · (2016 - 2020)

New Mexico State University

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2002 - 2006)

Onate High School - Las Cruces, NM High School Diploma · (1999 - 2002)